/*global angular */

angular.module('mathSkills').value('data5_3', {
    title: '5.3 Identifying Prime and Composite Numbers',
    path: '5.3-identifying-prime-and-composite-numbers',
    children: [{
        title: 'Determine whether a Number is Prime or Composite',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Is 55 prime or composite?}',
                answer: '\\butgrp{\\row{\\but{Prime}{F}}{\\but{Composite}{T}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": false,
                    "help": '\\html{Solution<br><br>55 is composite because it is divisible by more than 1 and itself.}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Determine whether a Number is Prime or Composite',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Is 41 prime or composite?}',
                answer: '\\butgrp{\\row{\\but{Prime}{T}}{\\but{Composite}{F}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": false,
                    "help": '\\html{Solution<br><br>41 is prime because it is divisible by only 1 and itself}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Determine whether a Number is Prime or Composite',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Is 71 prime or composite?}',
                answer: '\\butgrp{\\row{\\but{Prime}{T}}{\\but{Composite}{F}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": false,
                    "help": '\\html{Solution<br><br>71 is prime because it is divisible by only 1 and itself.}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Determine whether a Number is Prime or Composite',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Is 17 prime or composite?}',
                answer: '\\butgrp{\\row{\\but{Prime}{T}}{\\but{Composite}{F}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": false,
                    "help": '\\html{Solution<br><br>17 is prime because it is divisible by only 1 and itself.}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Determine whether a Number is Prime or Composite',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Is 56 prime or composite?}',
                answer: '\\butgrp{\\row{\\but{Prime}{F}}{\\but{Composite}{T}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": false,
                    "help": '\\html{Solution<br><hr>56 is composite because it is divisible by more than 1 and itself}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Determine whether a Number is Prime or Composite',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Is 90 prime or composite?}',
                answer: '\\butgrp{\\row{\\but{Prime}{F}}{\\but{Composite}{T}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": false,
                    "help": '\\html{Solution<br><br>90 is composite because it is divisible by more than 1 and itself}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Determine whether a Number is Prime or Composite',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Is 11 prime or composite?}',
                answer: '\\butgrp{\\row{\\but{Prime}{T}}{\\but{Composite}{F}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": false,
                    "help": '\\html{Solution<br><br>11 is prime because it is divisible by only 1 and itself.}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Determine whether a Number is Prime or Composite',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Is 118 prime or composite?}',
                answer: '\\butgrp{\\row{\\but{Prime}{F}}{\\but{Composite}{T}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": false,
                    "help": '\\html{Solution<br><br>118 is composite because it is divisible by more than 1 and itself.}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Determine whether a Number is Prime or Composite',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Is 111 prime or composite?}',
                answer: '\\butgrp{\\row{\\but{Prime}{F}}{\\but{Composite}{T}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": false,
                    "help": '\\html{Solution<br><br>111 is composite because it is divisible by more than 1 and itself.}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Divisibility Test on Whole Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Is 185 prime or composite?}',
                answer: '\\butgrp{\\row{\\but{Prime}{F}}{\\but{Composite}{T}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": false,
                    "help": '\\html{Solution<br><br>185 is composite because it is divisible by more than 1 and itself.}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }]
});
